[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What ocean fish migrates from the Pacific Ocean to the Columbia River to spawn at the end of their life cycles?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Steelhead salmon (Rainbow trout)", "Coho salmon", "Chinook salmon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The source of the Amazon, the widest river in the world, is located in this area of Peru.", "correct_answer": "Calillona", "incorrect_answers": ["Arequipa", "Lima", "Juliaca"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name he glands that produce hormones.", "correct_answer": "endocrine glands", "incorrect_answers": ["salivary glands", "sweat glands", "oil glands"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What food results in negative calories when eaten?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Carrots", "Celery", "Radishes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which of these movies has Bruce Willis made cameo appearances as himself?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Oceans Twelve", "The Player", "Thats Adequate"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of diamond is the rarest on the planet?", "correct_answer": "Red", "incorrect_answers": ["Black", "Purple", "Orange"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The village of East Hampton was shocked upon learning that the two eccentric occupants of the dilapidated Grey Gardens estate were harboring not only cats, but what unusual animals in their attic?", "correct_answer": "Raccoons", "incorrect_answers": ["Chickens", "Bats", "Goats"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Michael Ballack, Franz Beckenbauer, Oliver Kahn, and J\u00fcrgen Klinsmann all played for this team.", "correct_answer": "Bayern Munich", "incorrect_answers": ["Wolfsburg", "Schalke 04", "Bayer Leverkusen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What bizarre food would pigs occasionally eat, being omnivores?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Tree bark", "Their young", "Rotting carcasses"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All iPods come in one and the same shape.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What prehistoric creatures threaten the only woman taking part in the expedition in the movie Journey to the Center of the Earth?", "correct_answer": "Prehistoric reptiles", "incorrect_answers": ["Cavebears", "Giant snakes", "Cavemen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the funny name of Judy Greers character in the 1999 comedy-drama movie Jawbreaker?", "correct_answer": "Fern Mayo", "incorrect_answers": ["Germ Apes", "Hump Scratchington", "Perm Pistachio"]}]